<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Janja Brendel</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Janja Brendel</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Janja Brendel</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a PhD candidate Humboldt-University of Berlin. Since 2016, I have been working as a research and teaching assistant at the Institute of Accounting and Auditing at the chair of Joachim Gassen. Before returnng to my academic roots, I took a detour through corporate development jobs and through the thrill of investment banking (M&amp;amp;A and restructuring) where I worked in Europe and China. This detour helped me to better understand some of the concepts I have learned at school and university and it also helped me to see potential for interesting questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My interest in academic work has started at LSE where I completed my post- and undergraduate studies. Professors gave us a lot (really  a lot!!!) of research papers to read and raised a lot of conceptual issues during their lectures. This helped to train us to become independet thinkers and future scholars. In hindsight, this was probably the best training for my PhD. While completing the course work of the Berlin Doctoral Program of Economics and Management Science (BDPEMS), it also helped me to start to work on my own projects. Still obsessed with learning new things on an ongoing basis, I still enjoy going to interesting courses, such as courses on machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am interested in empirical financial accounting research in general. Particularly, I am interested in understanding the determinants and consequences of firms’ financial transparency as well as the consequences of disclosure regulation in capital markets. I have a distinct interest in short sellers as well as financial institutions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
